<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="150546" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="TransitTimetables" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Real timetables for public transport — fixed departures, auto-sized fleets and terminus timing points. Works for buses, trams, trains, metros, ferries and planes." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<LongDescription>
Turn any public-transport line into a scheduled service. Works for every passenger type: buses, trams, trains, metros, ferries and aircraft.

Per line you opt in and set:
- a first departure time and peak / off-peak / night intervals (the peak windows are configurable),
- the mod then DERIVES how many vehicles the line needs to hold that headway, and raises the game's vehicle-count ceiling so the derived fleet is never clamped,
- a terminus stop (timing point) where early vehicles are held to the scheduled departure, and where surplus vehicles retire — after finishing their loop and dropping passengers, not mid-route.

Select any stop to open a printed-timetable departure board for every line that serves it, listed from the first departure of the day. Day-only and night-only lines only show and run the intervals that apply to them, and a night line is scheduled inside the night window.

No timetable set = the line runs exactly like vanilla. Everything is controlled from the line's own info panel plus a floating departures board.

Source (open source, MIT): https://github.com/AmicusDeus/TransitTimetables

Made with Claude Code's Opus 4.8 and Fable 5 models.
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.2.4" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.6.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times. Supported values are "Landmark Buildings", "San Fransisco Set", "Beach Properties", "Urban Promenades", "Modern Architecture"-->
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>
v0.2.4 — easier time and interval setting

- First departure now steps in 5 minutes instead of 15, so you can finally set times like 06:05 or 07:25. New -1h / +1h buttons keep big changes quick, and it now wraps around midnight instead of sticking at 00:00 (so a late-night first departure is a couple of clicks down, not a trip through the whole day).
- Each interval (peak / off-peak / night) gains -10 / +10 buttons next to the -1 / +1, so reaching something like 16 minutes takes a couple of clicks instead of sixteen.

Previously, in v0.2.3

- Vehicles depart on their scheduled minute again. v0.2 accidentally made a timetabled vehicle wait for passengers who were still walking up, which pushed departures past their posted time. That was never the intent: a timetable should keep the line ON time and let anyone who misses it take the next departure. Reverted.

- Fixed a serious hidden problem, and repaired the damage. Until now this mod switched OFF each timetabled line's vehicle "unbunching" (the behaviour that keeps vehicles evenly spaced) — and that change was written permanently into your saved city. The game has no setting for unbunching and never restores it, so uninstalling this mod would have left those lines unable to space themselves out FOREVER, with nothing to explain it and no way to fix it. The mod no longer touches that setting at all (it turned out to be unnecessary), and it now REPAIRS any line a previous version affected.

  If you have used timetables before: load your city once with this version and save it, and your lines are repaired automatically.

Previously:
- v0.2.2 — the night window now defaults to 22:00-06:00 to match the game's own transport night (existing settings are untouched; drag "Night end" to 6 if you want it).
- v0.2.1 — fixed a vehicle boarding near the end of a day-only/night-only line's window freezing at the stop for the rest of the day, blocking every other line serving that stop.
	</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/AmicusDeus/TransitTimetables" />
	<!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
