<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="150546" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="TransitTimetables" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Real timetables for public transport — fixed departures, auto-sized fleets and terminus timing points. Works for buses, trams, trains, metros, ferries and planes." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<LongDescription>
Turn any public-transport line into a scheduled service. Works for every passenger type: buses, trams, trains, metros, ferries and aircraft.

Per line you opt in and set:
- a first departure time and peak / off-peak / night intervals (the peak windows are configurable),
- the mod then DERIVES how many vehicles the line needs to hold that headway, and raises the game's vehicle-count ceiling so the derived fleet is never clamped,
- a terminus stop (timing point) where early vehicles are held to the scheduled departure, and where surplus vehicles retire — after finishing their loop and dropping passengers, not mid-route.

Select any stop to open a printed-timetable departure board for every line that serves it, listed from the first departure of the day. Day-only and night-only lines only show and run the intervals that apply to them, and a night line is scheduled inside the night window.

No timetable set = the line runs exactly like vanilla. Everything is controlled from the line's own info panel plus a floating departures board.

Source (open source, MIT): https://github.com/AmicusDeus/TransitTimetables

Made with Claude Code's Opus 4.8 and Fable 5 models.
	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.2.83" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.6.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times. Supported values are "Landmark Buildings", "San Fransisco Set", "Beach Properties", "Urban Promenades", "Modern Architecture"-->
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>
v0.2.83 (alpha) — works with Realistic Trips (Time2Work), plus terminus points at stations

- NEW: a "Keep achievements enabled" toggle (General settings) — keeps Cities: Skylines II achievements available while the mod is active. On by default. Settings now also save to disk the moment you change them, so they survive a crash or a non-clean exit.

- NEW (ALPHA): compatibility with slow-time mods like Realistic Trips / Time2Work. A new setting, "Adapt to slow-time mods" (ON by default), measures the real length of a day at runtime, so on a stretched clock your departures, stop times and vehicle counts stay correct instead of running early. With no such mod installed it changes nothing at all. IMPORTANT: this compatibility path has NOT been tested in-game against Realistic Trips yet — it is an alpha; please report anything odd. Under Realistic Trips your timetabled lines will correctly run fewer vehicles than before.

- NEW: terminus points at STATIONS. You can now set a line's terminus at a train, metro, airport or harbour station — not just roadside bus/tram stops. Clicking the station opens its departures board listing every line that stops there.

- NEW: a "Set as terminus" button on every line's row in the departures board, so at a shared stop or a multi-platform station you can set the terminus for any line directly, without opening each line first. (A "Set as terminus for all lines here" shortcut appears when two or more lines share the stop.)

- Tidied the settings page: removed "Max vehicles per line" (no longer needed — timetabled lines already run their full fleet uncapped) and the developer-only "Analyze shared stops" toggle.

Earlier versions: v0.2.7 fixed the vanilla "Assigned Vehicles" slider distortion; v0.2.6 stopped slightly-late buses from waiting a whole cycle and added a 2-minute minimum dwell; v0.2.5 reworked the panel steppers and made the first-departure display honest; v0.2.3 restored on-time departures and auto-repaired vehicle unbunching; v0.2.1-v0.2.2 were hotfixes.
	</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/AmicusDeus/TransitTimetables" />
	<!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
	<AccessLevel Value="Public" />
</Publish>
